https://pennine-sc.co.uk/data-privacy-policy/

PSC Data Privacy Policy
Pennine Sailing Club respects the privacy of its members and guests ensuring that it interacts with all users of the clubs facilities in line with current legislation including the General Data Protection Regulations 2018.
We collect and process personal information for the following reasons:
To administer membership records and collect fees
To publicise events and activities at the Club
To maintain duty registers and notify members of their duties
To publish race results
To manage member equipment stored at the club
To provide information to students attending courses, open meetings or other club events
To comply with the clubs constitutions and requirements of the RYA for the club training centre
We collect and store the following information:
Contact information for members, temporary members and guests using the club facilities (e.g. name, address, email address, telephone number)
Details of members equipment stored at the club
Medical and dietary information for those attending training courses
Attendance and characteristics information for analysis and reporting
Photos and videos of members and visitors while using the club facilities
CCTV recordings for security
We share this information with:
Officers of the club to enable them to fulfil their duties including, administration, membership and training
The RYA but not including personal information
Race result recording
CCTV recordings are periodically reviewed for security purposes and on request maybe shared with the clubs insurers and the police
Videos and photos of members and visitors using the club facilities are posted on our website and other social media channels
We will not share your personal information with any third parties apart from those stated here without your prior advance permission.
Requesting access to or updating your personal data
You have the right to request access to or change the information that we hold about you. To make such a request please email to membership@pennine-sc.co.uk
May 2018
